Calum Boone

email cell LinkedIn calum.boone@gmail.com

856.725.2440

linkedin.com/in/calum-boone/

profile

Energetic and innovative professional transitioning from data management and analytics to UX/UI design. My passion for simplifying complex processes and improving usability is driven by a strong focus on delivering exceptional end-user experiences.

In my downtime, you'll find me creating music, diving into design projects, or enjoying live sports and music.

education

2018 — 2022 | Boston, MA

Northeastern University

Bachelor of Science Business Administration and Design

2014 — 2018 | Moorestown, NJ

Moorestown Friends School

High School Diploma

skills

design

Photoshop • Illustrator • InDesign • Premiere Pro • After Effects • Figma • Canva • FL Studio

management & analytics

Google Suite • Excel (advanced) • Microsoft Office Suite • JIRA • Asana • Notion • Visier • Salesforce • Looker/Looker Studio • Google BigQuery • Joomla • Sprout Social • SPSS • Google Analytics • Google Apps

computation & programming

SQL • HTML • CSS • JavaScript • ReactJS • D3.js • Java (basic)

experience

Sales Operations Analyst

Wayfair Boston, MA August 2022 – July 2023

- Developed ETL pipeline entirely in Google Sheets for QA program from 120+ tabs across 50 sheets, further enabled reporting capabilities for 2 other B2B QA programs.
- Cleaned over 27,000 reports and 500 folders in Salesforce, reducing volume by ~85%. Created a centralized repository for Sales agents.
- Maintained agent queue for Salesforce issues, triaging tickets between engineering teams and other ops. teams.
- Pulled monthly KPI reports and helped develop new KPIs for sales agent web activity and QA program health.

Digital Marketing Co-op

Natixis Investment Managers Boston, MA January 2021 – July 2021

- Managed scheduling of social media content.
 Automated a previously manual process to retrieve the weekly posts and apply google analytics tracking tags.
- Updated and maintained the website, such as posting articles, expanding on the Separately Managed Account offerings, developing site templates for SMA products, and implementing any organizational changes.
- Posted and updated monthly and quarterly holdings documents. Assisted in automating the process for updating all legal documents for the funds.

Design Intern

New York Brand Studios Toronto, ON, CAN June 2019 – August 2019

- Managed the shipping and storage of production and advertising samples, as well as updating and automating the shipping process in the office.
- Updated the internal production tracker for Q1, including adding data analysis ability and creating more usability.
- Compiled a report of over 190 failed inspections and provided key analysis showing the issues.
- Assisted in ordering and storage of over 600 advertising samples for quarterly photoshoot, as well as communicating with vendors to ensure delivery.

Flexible Fulfillment Team Member

Target Cherry Hill, NJ June – August 2018

- Fulfilled all aspects of online orders.
- Responsible for actively monitoring in-store pickups; occasionally responsible for back stocking, price changes, assisting customers on the floor, special projects, closing the backroom during closing shifts and maintaining cleanliness.